<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JEAN JOOHYUN OH</title>
    <link>https://jeanjhoh.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JEAN JOOHYUN OH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://jeanjhoh.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://jeanjhoh.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeanjhoh.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a PhD candidate in the Management Division at Columbia Business School.
I study when and how entrepreneurship operates as a channel for individual upward mobility and as a solution to social problems. My research is at the intersection of entrepreneurship, inequality, and business and society, focusing on two related themes: (1) how individuals’ socioeconomic origins affect their entrepreneurial decision-making and outcomes; and (2) how entrepreneurs are motivated by creating social impact and solving specific problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://jeanjhoh.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeanjhoh.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>You can find my latest CV here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://jeanjhoh.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeanjhoh.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Peer-Reviewed Publications What Motivates Innovative Entrepreneurs? Evidence from a Global Field Experiment
(with Jorge Guzman and Ananya Sen) Management Science, 2020.
Mapping the Class Ceiling: The Social Class Disadvantage for Attaining Management Positions
(with Paul Ingram) Academy of Management Discoveries, 2022.
Climate Change Framing and Innovator Attention: Evidence from an Email Field Experiment
(with Jorge Guzman and Ananya Sen) Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences (PNAS), 2023.
Working Papers and Works in Progress Privilege or Humble Beginnings?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
